

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

in LinkedIn: mehdi-hoseiniTwitter/Mehdi\_HoseiniPGithub/Mehdi-Hp

Mehdi.HoseiniPajooh@gmail.com

+98903 54 21 212

Tehran, Iran

I am a Front-End developer/engineer, passionate about JavaScript, how it really works and its underlying features.

I also pursue the world of JavaScript engines and browsers. Vue is the framework of my taste, and I'm using it since its first release. I'm also experienced with NodeJS and MongoDB mostly for my personal projects.

#### EXPERIENCE

# Front-End Developer / NodeJS Developer at Alibaba group

2019 — Now ♥ Tehran, Iran

- + Working on a new Content Management System from scratch, called "Traffic"
- + Develop a CDN service for working with images
- + Develop a brand new content/layout editor with Vue
- + Published bunch of plugins and packages on npm

## Front-End Developer at @ Orchid Pharmed

2018 — 2019 **♀** Tehran, Iran

- + Maintained and optimized front-end of a big legacy web application called eCRF that was written with jQuery and ES4.
- + Made a secret chat web aplication from scratch with Vue for company's internal usage.

# Web Developer at Peivast Monthly

2012 — 2016 • Tehran, Iran

- + UX design, UI design, front-end and back-end development of the official website using wordpress as CMS
- + Responsible for website's content
- + Social networks management
- + Animating covers for each number using Adobe Animate

## OSS



#### https://ghostax.netlify.com

A renderless vue framework. Heavily relying on scoped-slot concept.

#### vue-container-query-2

https://npmjs.com/package/vue-container-query-2

Vue plugin to work with container queries

Other stuff on Github and npm...

#### EDUCATION

## Bachelor's Degree

Software Engineering

At Scinece and Culture Collage

2018 — Now • Tehran, Iran

# Associate's Degree

Information Technology

At Shamsipour Technical Collage

2018 — Now ♀ Tehran, Iran

#### SKILLS

JavaScript — Vue

CSS — PostCSS — SASS

HTML — Various Template Engines

Build Tools — Webpack, Gulp

NodeJS — ExpressJS - hapi

Mongodb — Mongoose

Git / TFS

Very little of ThreeJS, jQuery, AngularJS, React, PHP

# IUSE

VUEX, Flux style stores

Storybook Jest Cypress

CSS Namespaces: BEM, SMACSS

ATOMIC Design

Robust Project Folder Structure

Paper Prototyping

Linux as General Workflow

Adobe XD

Github / Gitlab





